In today's world, people see sex
as more than just a means of reproduction.
It's evolved to mean different things
to different people,
filling a distinct individual void.
And which country ranks
amongst the lowest in the world
in terms of frequency
and satisfaction from sex?
Japan.
But when the sun goes down…
that's when people reveal
their true selves.
But once that sun rises again,
they revert back
to the mask they wear in public.
Nobody talks about sex,
and it's as if it's nothing more
than a passing fancy.
But is that really the truth?
Or is there something hidden underneath?
If you're someone
who's struggling with sex,
- I'm the guy who can help you.
- Oh!
Please ensure you have
all your belongings before leaving…
- We are stopping at…
- Excuse me. Sorry. Pardon me.
Oh! Ah!
Oh…
What is that?
- Oh…
- Wow!
Ah…
Uh…
Uh… sorry, my bad.
Uh, th-those are
for educational purposes only.
Educational tools. Tools!
Not recreational.
Ugh!
SHIMOTORI CLINIC
COME TO US WITH ANY SEXUAL CONCERNS
So they thought
you were a perv again, huh?
You love to disappear
into your own little world, don't ya?
You think you might
learn your lesson someday?
That maybe it's not a good idea
to be carrying around
a bag bursting with sex toys.
I had a lecture at the university.
Think about how it makes me look.
I have to go pick you up
every time you do something like that.
Sorry, I'll remember that.
Excuse… Ow!
Excuse me?
- Goddamn it! That hurts!
- It's okay, just breathe.
It's so bad that I can't even
tell how much pain I'm in anymore.
- How did, um…
- Oh, damn!
- Okay, no. That might hurt. That's bad.
- Doctor, maybe olive oil?
Good. Thank you.
- I can't take much more.
- Huh?
You know… it's not exactly what I do here.
I mean, the sign says,
"Come to us with any sexual concerns."
Well, yes. But, uh…
This is more like plastic
and reconstructive surgery or, uh…
urology, even, I'd say.
Ah.
But I guess sexual therapy
can sound a little confusing.
The other day, I had an older woman
beg me to castrate some stray--
- I don't mean to be rude, but get it out!
- Uh-huh, I'm sorry.
Ah, just apply a little bit of oil here.
It's going all over it! I can feel it! Ah!
- It's okay, just breathe slowly.
- You'll be all good.
- I'll gently pull it out.
- You're gonna rip it off!
- It's gone, it's gone, it's gone!
- No, it's not. Breathe.
I'll go slow and be gentle.
- Ah, you got it, you got it, you got it!
- Please hold still, sir.
- It's snapping!
- It's almost out, we're almost there.
Aah… uh…
There we are.
Ah!
- Check it.
- Oh! Uh…
- Uh…
- Aah!
Oh, thanks so much!
- You're a lifesaver.
- Oh, man.
- So, how exactly…
- Oh, right.
How should I put this?
It was out of curiosity.
Or to be honest, I couldn't help myself.
Ah.
I've just been having
these erotic thoughts lately.
All day, every day. It's wild.
- Mmm.
- It makes me wanna try all these things.
- Like I'm reverting to a horny teenager.
- Aah.
I thought it would go away,
once I became more of an adult, ya know?
- Instead, it just kept getting worse.
- Mmm.
It's anywhere. On the train,
or at work. Literally anywhere.
You're talking about masturbation?
Yeah… Wh-what if…
it never gets any better?
Do you… do you think that I'm sick?
Hmm. It's a hard thing to define.
Hmm.
Marin, you got a sec?
Are we done for the day?
You've got one new patient later on,
otherwise, basically nothing.
- Good to know.
- It's actually not good.
We're gonna go out of business.
Allow me to introduce myself
again to you.
I'm Dr. Shimotori.
Uh, does that say sex therapist?
It does, yeah.
Would you like to try it?
Might do you good.
Uh, yeah.
Eyes open. There's no reason
to feel embarrassed.
Ah!
Now, let's
take a deep breath and try climbing.
No, I-I'm sorry. I don't think I can.
- I'm gonna have an anxiety attack.
- You can trust me.
I'll make sure that nothing goes wrong
and you don't fall.
Try the blue ones.
There's literally nothing
for us to do around here.
Yeah.
Look, it's good, it's not stressful, but…
Uh, no, it's not good at all.
The business isn't sustainable.
If you move your right foot next,
then it'll be easy.
I'm more freaked out that he's
taking on all these weird-ass clients.
- Good!
- People's junk in milk bottles.
- Or castrating random cats.
- Oh my God! I did it! I made it!
- Good for you! You did it, see?
- Aah!
It's not his job to judge.
He's a professional, his job is
to hear the patient out no matter what.
Does he have to go rock climbing for that?
I won't pretend
to understand what he does.
My job is to sit here and answer
all these calls we're not getting.
- Ah! Ah!
- I got you.
- You'll be fine, trust me. You're good.
- Ah.
Aah!
There, not so bad.
I can't believe it! Oh!
That was amazing!
Uh, and also,
I think you holding the rope
helped me with my confidence.
Hm.
Therapy will be good for you.
Trust me on this.
Be warned, I might not be able
to climb for you or even next to you.
But I'll show you how not to fall,
and maybe even suggest
the right route for your issues.
Oh!
That's so cool.
Those climbing holds
look like a yawning face.
Ah!
- Hmm.
- You're lucky, doctor, huh?
You don't worry about sex at all, do you?
One thing you can be sure of…
When it comes to sex,
no one is sure about anything.
Hey, I'm back.
Amaka is gonna be a new regular.
That's great, but your other
new patient is waiting.
What? Who?
Akira Hayama. He didn't want to wait here,
so I showed him into the therapy room.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
My name is Dr. Shimotori,
and I'm a sex therapist.
Ah. That's Yuta, my nurse.
He works with me.7
He sits in and takes notes for me.
PATIENT QUESTIONNAIRE
What was it that brought you
here today, then?
Addiction, actually.
Sexual addiction.
I'm happily married with a child.
But sometimes it can be
three people in one day.
I don't care if it's some kind of pill.
Whatever. I just need you to cure it.
So it could be with numerous,
anonymous partners, correct?
- Other than your wife?
- No.
It's my wife.
She's the one who's addicted to sex.
Ms. Natsume makes
an incredible herbal tea.
What's it today?
It's lemongrass and spearmint. Mmm.
Please, go ahead.
So, where's your husband?
He prefers that no one sees him here.
He's killing time somewhere.
Oh. Sorry.
Don't worry, it's fine.
Ah… mind if I ask you a few questions?
How often do you have sex
with your husband?
Uh, how often?
I know it can be hard to talk about it.
But whatever you can share.
Oh. Huh.
Uh…
It's been quite a while, but…
Before that, it was once
every two months, I suppose.
And did you get any pleasure from it?
Um, yes. I guess.
On a scale of one to five?
- A four, maybe?
- Hmm.
And what about the stiffness
of your husband's penis? How's that?
- How is it?
- You know. Like a konnyaku?
A grapefruit?
A mandarin orange? Or an apple?
Which is closest? Yes.
- Are you serious?
- Oh, absolutely. Yes.
We use a scale called EHS,
Erection Hardness Score,
to evaluate the stiffness of an erection.
Oh. Huh.
Uh…
Um… a grapefruit, then?
Uh, because, well, mandarins…
I just don't like the taste of mandarins.
You don't?
Well, I don't mind them so much
if they're soft
but, you know, not if they're, um…
Um… I don't like them
if they're really hard.
Oh, that's right! They are a lot better
when they're soft, aren't they?
Yeah, but sometimes,
you think they're soft, but…
they're actually just all dried out.
Yeah, I really hate that.
So let me ask you,
when you peel a mandarin,
do you remove that white stringy stuff,
or do you leave it on?
Oh, no! I take it off all the time.
Really? What a waste!
Come on.
Interesting.
How so?
Well, you spent almost half the time
talking about fruit and mandarin oranges.
Yeah. I guess I did do that, I suppose.
But did you ever really know
what a kumquat was?
No, but I don't think that was…
There you go.
What? What does that…
Should we really charge
a consultation fee for that?
Well, she certainly looked more relaxed
than when she came in.
Yeah?
Maybe she'll feel more comfortable
talking about things next time.
All right, I'm takin' off.
- Thanks for a great day!
- Have a good night.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah, thanks for a great day.
Ahem.
I don't know. I just don't get it.
I mean, she's
this sweet-looking housewife,
who does laundry and raises a kid,
but who's also addicted to sex!
You know you're talking out loud, right?
I'm just saying, it's weird that,
when her husband got pissed off
after he found out about her first affair,
she says she's sorry and begs him
not to leave her and he forgives her.
But she keeps doing it, and now it seems
like it's gotten even worse than before.
Yeah, well, that's
pretty much what addiction is.
Isn't it?
Jeez. I just don't get it at all.
You don't have any hang-ups, Yuta?
- No sexual issues?
- You got that right. Not a single one.
Me and my lady…
We give each other all that we can handle.
Ugh! Too much information.
Oh, yeah?
I just mean that
lots of people have issues.
And it's a good thing that
Dr. Shimotori is around to help them.
Huh.
You ever wonder what his sex life is like?
Not really.
I've never heard about anything.
I wonder if he's got
any weird-ass fetishes.
I wouldn't know.
Hey, you think he goes to any kinky clubs?
If you're looking for a good
time, come with me. I'll blow your mind.
BOOBS
COLLEGE GIRLS
Ah. Excuse me!
How ya doin'? Looking for a lady?
- That's right. You are.
- Hey, baby.
We all are, aren't we?
Over here, check this out!
- 3,000 for two hours.
- Like what you see, baby?
- Oh. Ah.
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
Uh… No, no. Don't worry, it was my fault.
Ah.
Yumi, is that you?
- Huh?
- Oh.
I-I'm sorry. I thought
you were someone else. I…
Wait. Uh…
Ichito, is that you?
Uh… Yeah.
Oh, wow.
SEX ADDICTION
It's, uh…
great to see you.
Oh. Uh, yeah.
These are, um… Well, they're for…
Uh, for work. Yeah.
Um. Ah…
- Ah. Here's my card.
- Oh.
PHYSICIAN / SEX THERAPIST
ICHITO SHIMOTORI
You're a sex therapist?
Ah.
Yeah. That's right.
VELUNA COSMETIC SURGERY CONSULTATION
It's amazing running into you here.
Uh, I'm here for my job.
- Ah.
- Well, I better go.
- Oh.
- See ya.
FIELD REPORTER
YUMI ICHINOSE
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Come on in.
Actor Kosuke Matsudo
has issued a public apology
after news broke
of a late-night rendezvous
with young actress Shiori Suzukaze.
Suzukaze called a news conference
to make that apology.
I took to the street to talk
to a few people
and gauge the public's reaction.
He's a married man.
I think it's inexcusable.
I think people should give her a break.
I just think that's the cost of fame.
- It's not like she…
- Push in tighter, camera one.
- Back to the studio in five…
- When you're famous…
- Four. Three…
- She could have been more forthcoming.
So that's what
some of our viewers had to say.
If I'm being honest,
I'm not so sure forcing Suzukaze
to have a press conference
was the best way to handle that.
But that's just my humble opinion.
And it would appear that at least half
of our viewers agree with you.
Stay tuned to find out
what the weather has in store for us.
- That's it for today, people.
- Thanks, everyone!
- Good work today people, well done!
- Good stuff, thank you!
- Just a few more weeks of this.
- Well-oiled machine!
- Good.
- Hello!
- Thanks.
- Mitarai.
- Yes?
- See you in 20.
- You bet, I'm gonna get changed.
- Great.
- Excuse me, Takuro?
- Hmm?
Do we really need to be reporting
on celebrities' dating life
on the evening news?
Mmm… I admit it's kind of borderline.
But the guy's having an affair
that cost him a contract.
Seems to me the public
wanna know about that.
Yeah, well, reporting on someone's
private romantic or sexual life…
I don't know, it just feels like
that's beneath us.
Look at you!
You shooting for a Pulitzer or something?
You're the epitome of purity.
That's what your audience wants from you.
- Oh, Miku!
- Hey, thanks for today.
- Thank you, that's a great outfit.
- Oh, thanks!
- Looked amazing on camera.
- I hoped so.
Yeah, the camera
definitely loves you! No question.
Aaah.
Boy, you just gotta love
producers, don't you?
Do we really? Great work today.
Yeah. Thanks. You too.
SHIMOTORI CLINIC
Yes. One moment, please.
- Doctor, you have a phone call.
- Yeah?
Last name Ichinose?
- Wha…
- Uh, right!
Ah, ah!
Hello, Dr. Shimotori speaking.
Hi, there, it's Yumi.
- Hi.
- I hope I'm not disturbing you at work.
Yes. I mean, uh, no.
Uh…
So…
I was wondering if you'd like
to have dinner sometime.
Oh. You mean food?
Yes. You up for it?
- Uh…
- Hey.
- It's a woman?
I am. Great.
Great. Where can I reach you?
- Away from work.
- Oh!
Right. Yeah, um…
I'll give you my line ID. Yeah. It's, uh,
S. H.
- I. M.
- In the three months I've been here?
- This is closest I've seen him to human.
- Yes, M, that's right. As in "mental."
Then O.
Doctor?
You look very happy today.
Huh?
You're all restless.
All right. Let's start, shall we?
Is it a girl?
We're gonna start now.
Now then, please tell me the first time
you had sex with someone
other than your husband.
The cause of the addiction
often lies in the very beginning.
The first time was…
- Have a good trip.
- Mmm. I'll call you later.
Mm-hm.
It was…
when my husband was away
on a long business trip.
- Bye, Mommy.
- Bye.
You would have thought
I'd gotten used to it by then, but…
Ah!
But for some reason,
I was suddenly afraid of being alone.
During the day,
when my daughter was at school,
I started going over
to friends, or restaurants.
More and more frequently.
I wasn't sure. I…
One of them was this man.
He was the owner
of the restaurant I liked.
I was babbling on,
when he stopped me and said…
"Your hands are amazing."
"They're so pretty,
'cause they look like they're dancing."
It made me feel so good.
I used to practice ballet
when I was a little girl.
Oh, boy, I'd, uh…
I'd kinda forgotten that.
Ever since then…
whenever I feel anxious or alone,
I end up having sex with someone.
I want you to know
I don't have an orgasm.
If I have sex with someone
other than my husband,
I don't feel pleasure.
But when I'm with my husband,
my body feels a kind of lightness.
Like I'm suspended in water.
And I feel secure.
But I don't feel that way
with other people.
No matter how much I move,
I can't reach the surface of the water.
Professor, I'd like to get your opinion
about all the recent moves
that the current government of Japan
has implemented
to correct the lower birthrate
in the country.
SION KASE
To begin with…
I feel that our government
has missed the mark on this.
- But there are other issues.
- No shocker there.
Another expert with a different opinion
than the rest of us.
How much do you think they get
for being on these shows?
I have no idea.
No one's ever asked me to be on.
…choosing their career…
Oh. Hello, Professor Kurusu.
Another leisurely day?
No patients coming in?
Hello, there!
Saikawa!
You're looking a lot better.
- Yeah, you think so?
- Uh-huh.
Looks like you got a bit of color.
You were white as a ghost when
you were with us. But you're back now.
- Having no patients can do it.
- Aah.
I'm sure Dr. Shimotori gives you
enough work to keep you busy.
Hmm? Yeah, I guess.
Working here is pretty cool.
Well…
…and difficulty…
In time, you'll know more.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
All right, then.
How about a little discussion
while we eat?
Mmm? So she feels no pleasure,
is that what she said?
That's right.
Ah.
That might explain why the husband
is looking for a solution, ah?
My feeling is that it's not so much
a hormonal abnormality
but a compulsive sexual behavior disorder.
Mm-hm.
Yes, sex can relieve stress for a time,
but where she's concerned,
she feels self-loathing after.
And to counter that,
she goes out and has sex again.
A vicious cycle.
So, then, it's not about
having a really strong sex drive.
Right. It's addictive behavior
that won't stop
unless they succumb to their desire.
So…
the important thing
about overcoming addiction
is regaining sobriety.
Oh, wait… Sobriety?
Alcoholics can't drink.
And a gambler can't bet.
It's the same
for a person addicted to sex.
That's the definition of sexual sobriety.
Oh. Sexual sobriety.
It's about not being controlled
by destructive behavior.
Being able to deal with
your own sexuality, on your terms.
And the first step she needs to take
is to recognize that.
So? How are you gonna do it?
Well, my first inclination was
to get them to try couples counseling.
But her husband won't do it.
So I want to try delving
a little further into it.
To get to the root of the issue.
The root, huh?
Oh. Yuta, it's your day off tomorrow.
You doing anything?
Eh?
It depends why you're asking.
I want you to come somewhere with me.
- Hm. This should be interesting.
- Hmm?
- He's totally free.
- Huh?
- You've got nothing.
- You have no idea what I've got!
Now you know why I recommended this place.
Huh?
Very good! Very good. Feel the stretch.
Come on everyone, lift!
That's right. No laughing.
- Concentrate.
- Point your toes.
Feel your legs getting longer.
Hey! Straighten that knee! And up!
- Ow!
- Good. Nice form.
Why am I doing this again?
This isn't my idea of a day off.
Hmm. Hey, you might just learn something.
You can put your legs down.
It's time for our jumps into plié.
Place both hands onto the barre and…
- Jump and jump and jump and jump.
- Jump, jump.
Very good, keep it up. Jump! Jump!
Now it's time to get into
the fifth position.
Plié! And plié. And change, and change.
Good, keep your neck long.
Now come forward, everyone.
Well done!
How did you like your free lesson?
I had no idea how stiff my body was.
Actually, you were wonderful.
You should be proud.
So what brought you to us today?
A friend recommended it.
Her name is Sena Hayama.
Sena…
Good, next position.
How's Sena doing?
Oh, wow, that's great!
Oh, I haven't seen her in so long!
Yeah, she's doing great.
Oh, Sena, she was wonderful.
Always so happy when she was dancing.
Her mother was
just as dedicated as she was.
Sadly, she hurt her hand
when she was in junior high.
It really affected her a lot.
- Her hand?
- Oh, yes.
In ballet, the movement
of a dancer's hands is so important.
She just never seemed to be able
to dance the way she used to,
and that bothered her so much.
But not as much as it bothered her mother.
That woman was a real perfectionist.
At some point,
she just stopped coming, which was…
so sad.
- Good!
- Hmm.
Why would people choose to do that?
That was hard!
But I'm so happy we came.
I feel like we got
to the root of the problem.
Ow.
Aah…
The combination
of her perfectionist mother,
with an imperfect self
and an injured hand.
Sena's hand may just be
the root of her problem
and the trigger for her addiction.
What is that exactly? Do you know?
- Oh!
- "The epitome of purity?"
What does that even mean?
Okay, sure, maybe I had a more
wholesome image when I was a weather girl.
But I'm not a kid anymore. I'm 32!
Wait a minute.
We're the same age, aren't we?
Uh. Yeah, 32.
We were in the same grade.
That's right!
Hah! Duh!
Mmm.
Wholesome.
When do I get to shed that image?
I didn't become a reporter to get
all dolled up and wear pretty clothes.
Sorry.
We haven't seen each other
since high school, and here I am whining.
It's all right.
I don't have anyone
to talk to about stuff like this.
Well, you do now. You can talk to me.
Whatever you want to talk about,
I'm here for you.
You haven't changed, Ichito.
I remember that
you'd keep quiet and let me go on and on,
even back then.
Yeah, well… I liked it.
Look at you. Always the professional.
Uh… So I guess I'm,
uh, a little worked up.
So… I mean, it's been a while.
I don't even know
how to act around you anymore.
Do you remember…
that day?
The festival?
Why didn't you…
ever show up?
That's, uh…
It's, uh…
- It's…
- Aah!
Silly me! I'm sorry.
Forget it.
You, uh, you transferred schools
right after that.
I had no way of contacting you.
I was just curious…
what had happened, that's all.
Aah.
But we're all grown-up now.
So there's no need to rehash everything.
526, uh…
5-2-6.
ON THE WAY TO PICK UP
ICHITO SHIMOTORI
O-526
Aah.
My bad. I should've asked
the restaurant to call.
- I'm not well versed with this stuff.
- Don't worry.
Let me see?
Well, the driver's lost.
O-526! Aah…
O-5… Over here!
Over here!
Uh…
Right here!
Thank you.
This was fun. I'd love to see you again.
Yeah, sure.
Good night, then.
Hello.
- Hey, what's up?
- Get over here, it's an emergency!
She met a guy on a dating app.
Apparently they used box cutters
in some kind of sex play.
So what? They cut each other?
From what I gathered, yeah.
Blood play of some kind.
The bleeding wouldn't stop,
so she was taken to the hospital.
What about the guy?
Looks like he took off.
Let's go.
Uh…
And what are you here for?
I wish I could've helped
before this happened. I still want to.
Please forgive me.
Well, at least this proves something.
Sex therapy's a load of crap.
A complete waste of time.
Mr. Hayama!
I'd like to try one last thing.
If you could both just come see me.
There's a prescription I could give you.
Let's go.
Follow me.
Is this your vacation home, doctor?
Oh, no.
I could never afford a place like this.
You want to tell us
why you dragged us out here?
Ah, of course.
This is the prescription
I was talking about.
Those coffee beans were incredible.
Ethiopian?
Mm-hm.
All right.
- There.
- Thank you.
There you go.
Sorry for the wait.
Thank you very much.
So, uh…
What is all this?
Are you two going to tell us
the secret to a happy marriage?
No.
These two are not officially married.
What?
They are in what's called
an open marriage.
Their relationship allows them
to have partners other than themselves.
I have another husband.
And I love my wife,
but I can't get an erection anymore.
After we had children,
we just stopped having sex.
Our relationship as a married couple
became strained,
and that's when
Dr. Shimotori suggested it.
And how did
this open marriage work for you?
It was exciting again.
We're so much happier now
in our relationship.
I didn't feel the pressure of having
to sleep with my wife anymore.
And I no longer had those guilty feelings
that I couldn't perform.
It was such a load off my mind.
One of the most dangerous
things about addiction
is the escalation of it.
Having encounters with numerous
anonymous partners can also be very risky.
In this scenario,
this approach could be
a very powerful prescription,
because it could narrow down the object
of your addiction to a single person.
Which would allow you
to become sexually sober.
I think this is your best way forward.
OPEN MARRIAGE CONTRACT
Are you kidding me with this?
I asked if you could cure my wife's
addiction
to having sex with random people.
And this is what you come up with?
This is…
I can't believe…
All right, fine.
No, wait!
After listening to you two, I…
I understand how this could work
for some relationships.
Um… I just don't know about ours.
I just don't know what to do.
So what?
What do we do now, Sena?
There is one…
One more prescription we can try.
You wanna give it a shot?
I've always hated this hand.
It's ugly.
And awkward.
And rough.
I had no idea that you felt that way.
It's such a shame.
And I wish I'd thought to tell you sooner.
I absolutely
love this sweet hand.
Her hand represented
all the pain that her soul endured
when she injured herself
when she was a child.
Her mother's need for perfection
brought back all the memories
of not being loved.
Every time she felt that pain in her hand,
those are the memories
that came flooding back.
Of not being loved, and trying
to feel it through sexual contact.
So loving her hand allowed her to be free.
And that…
was the missing prescription
in this specific case of mine.
To reaffirm the feeling
that she was loved,
despite the fact that she had been hurt.
But this was only the starting point
for what would serve
as her permanent treatment.
In Japan, sex therapy
is still pretty new to us.
And sadly, some people still think
about it as something dirty.
And many are also reluctant
to talk about their sexual issues,
even among friends.
And that's why I want
to try and change that,
so we can have
a more open dialogue about it.
Because
when it comes to sex, no one
is sure about anything.
Sexology, that's your thing, right?
What?
Sexology.
Oh.
Yes.
Academic freedom is one thing,
but damaging the reputation of this school
is quite another.
Dean Toyahara!
How are you?
Yeah, uh, sexology
is one hot subject these days.
He's only a guest lecturer right now,
but I'm hoping to convince him
to teach here regularly.
As a personal favor.
Hah. Yeah.
Huh.
- Good night.
- Good night. Mmm.
- Come here, you!
- Oh! Oh, what?
Come on, let's hit another bar!
No, that's it for me.
No!
Come on, we're just getting started!
- Let's have one more!
- Ah!
- I'm seriously done, I'm going home.
- There are so many more bars to go to!
- Come home with me?
- Oh!
All right, let's do this.
FIELD REPORTER
YUMI ICHINOSE
I HAD SO MUCH FUN. I DRANK TOO MUCH…
I HAD FUN TOO. THANKS.
LET'S GRAB DRINKS AGAIN!
SURE.
YUMI ICHINOSE
BLOCK
DO YOU WANT TO BLOCK YUMI ICHINOSE?
CANCEL / BLOCK
YOU HAVE BLOCKED YUMI ICHINOSE
It happened 17 years ago.
And you haven't seen
your first love again since then.
Do you still have feelings for her?
I don't even have the right
to have those feelings.
Don't have the right?
No, I don't.
I don't have the right to love anyone.
Can't even imagine
myself having sex.
The reason I became a sex therapist…
is because I can't stand sex.